Self-motivated Junior Software Developer experienced in using front end programming languages to solve complex problems within a deadline. My passion towards software development has kept me dedicated in reaching personal goals. Working in fast paced environments has led me to become agile and adaptable in order to meet the needs of the service users.

## Skills

- Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Linux Systems, working with the terminal.
- Knowledge of version control systems like GitHub.
- Actively working through resources like FreeCodeCamp and TheOdinProject.
- Actively working on projects like my portfolio website.
- Able to manage and carry out multiple projects at a time.
- Able to compromise and collaborate comfortably within a team.

## **Work History**

2022-02-Current

Domestic Operative

OCS, Ipswich Hospital, Ipswich, Suffolk

 Work efficiently within a ward to keep the space clean and organized for service users.

2019-09-2021-10

Care Support Worker

Jeian Residential Care Home, Ipswich, Suffolk

- Documented vitals, behaviours and medications in client medical records.
- Entertained, conversed and read aloud to keep patients mentally alert.

2019-04-2019-08

**Domiciliary Care Worker** 

Fountain of Health, Ipswich, Suffolk

- Utilized time management to handle tasks at pace.
- Assisted disabled clients to support independence and well-being.

2018-06-2019-02

Support Worker

Danshell Ltd, Colchester, Essex

- Developed rapport to create safe and trusting environment for care.
- Completed entries in log books, journals and care plans to accurately document and report patient progress.

## Education

A-Levels: Mathematics, Psychology, Sociology, General Studies, Photography-June 2017 Northgate Sixth Form, Ipswich

GCSEs: Mathematics, Statistics, English Literature, English Language, Science-June 2015 *Ipswich Academy, Ipswich*